https://titanengines.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Titan Engines is located at:Titan Engines2120 NW 10TH STFL, US352-732-8006It is Titan Engines' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while purchasing our products. This Privacy Policy applies to the Titan Engines store on www.titanengines.com (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "Titan Engines"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected when purchasing our product, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through this website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.- Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Titan Engines' store on this website choose to interact with us in ways that require Titan Engines to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Titan Engines gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we may ask you for your email address to contact you regarding your order.- SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.- E-commerceThose who engage in transactions with Titan Engines – by purchasing Titan Engines' services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Titan Engines collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Titan Engines.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Titan Engines may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Titan Engines' sole discretion. Titan Engines encourages visitors to our online store to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of Titan Engine's online store after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
OK
